Dima Snisarenko Frontend Developer

Last update: Wed Nov 15 2017 17:09:07 GMT+0100 (CET)

The online version is available at https://sneas.github.io/cv

Biography

Residence

Weesp, Dichtershof, NL

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/dmitry-snisarenko-74a4b830/

Email

snisarenkodima@gmail.com

Languages

English, Russian, Dutch on a primitive level

More than 10 years ago I started my career as a PHP developer and became Zend certificate in PHP 5.3. I still pretend to be a senior-level expert in LAMP stack. But front-end and UX have always been my passion. While trained to see tiny details as one-pixel bias or one-byte colour deviation I put my best effort in building neat, pleasant and fully-accessible UX components.

For the past 5 years, I've worked as a front-end developer. Mostly with Angular, Bootstrap + SASS for CSS, Webpack and NodeJS for automation routines. Working in a timely manner, considering budget, as an individual or part of a team. Technology, leadership, and problem-solving are the most prioritized directions for me.

Employment

KLM Royal Dutch Airlines

Senior frontend developer

Feb 2017 - present

Project: Real time mobile application used by KLM mechanics in Schiphol airport.

Angular 4 | Ionic 3 | Redux | RxJS | Typescript | SASS | Webpack 2 | Karma

Knab hypotheken

Senior frontend developer

Jun 2014 - Feb 2017

Project: Registration flow, mortgage tools

Responsibilities: Maintain existing project and provide new tools and components.

Main achievements: Backbone -> Angular 1.3 transition. Introduction of TDD with Karma and E2E with Protractor. Angular 1.3 -> Angular 1.5 transition.

```
AngularJS (Karma) (Protractor) (SASS) (Gulp) (Bootstrap) (Heroku
```

upwork.com

Senior frontend developer

Oct 2012 - Jun 2014

Probably one of the best companies I've ever worked with. A high traffic website. The biggest player on freelance job market.

Responsibilities: Maintain existing application, developed new features and components.

Main achievements: Introduction of TDD process with PHPUnit and qUnit. Job post template engine.



Education

Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering. Sevastopol State Technical University [2002 – 2007]

Certification

Zend Certified Engineer in PHP 5.3 - 24 Jan, 2011

Additional experience

Here you can find a complete list of my side/hobby projects: https://github.com/sneas.

Some projects I find exciting are shortly explained blow.

Component Library

https://github.com/sneas/component-library

The easiest way to create HTML component library for existing website.



A solution to CORS problem of Ionic and WKWebView

https://github.com/sneas/ionic-native-http-connection-backend

This project's become quite popular since Ionic made WKWebView a default web container.

Namespaced Bootstrap

https://github.com/sneas/bootstrap-sass-namespace

Non-conflicting bootstrap integration. You should consider using this project if you need to apply Bootstrap partially. ie to particular div of a page.

Bootstrap SASS